eatsomethingsexy.com 2019-06-30

# The Eat Something Sexy Privacy Policy -

The privacy of our visitors is very important to us. This privacy policy sets out how Eat Something Sexy, a Life of Reiley publication, uses and protects any information that you give while using [www.eatsomethingsexy.com](https://www.eatsomethingsexy.com/).

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### We use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. We also use Google Analytics and Facebook pixels and cookies.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Advertising

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, including Google Adsense and Amazon. These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using Google’s Ad Settings page at <https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated>. To opt out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit <https://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### For more information

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us via email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d5bcbbb3ba95b9bcb3b0bab3a7b0bcb9b0acfbb6bab8)

#### FREE APHRODISIAC NEWSLETTER

Subscribe to our free aphrodisiac newsletter

Thank you for subscribing.

Something went wrong.

We respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously

Scroll to top

#### FREE APHRODISIAC NEWSLETTER

Subscribe to our free aphrodisiac newsletter

Thank you for subscribing.

Something went wrong.

We respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously
